{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110338290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110338289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110338522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110338522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110339499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110339498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110340778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110340778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110343688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110343687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110344538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110344538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110344873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110344873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110346119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110346118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110349562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110349561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110350544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110350544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110350797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110350797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110351740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110351740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110354568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110354567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110355611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110355610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110356092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110356091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110360664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110360664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110360740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110360739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 92e5817f-1ffd-47a1-a80e-e1a84bf7907c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110375091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110375090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_pa-ve-mwo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110380183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110380183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_ja-pa-mwu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110385786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110385786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_re-yi-pa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110390373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110390373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_pa-mcha-mchi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110395530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110395530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_tha-pa-la"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110400014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110400014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_fa-mza-pa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110405018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110405018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_mzu-she-pa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110410283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110410283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_pa-nge-ndi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110416410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110416410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_nu-pe-pa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110433282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110433282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_mke-tha-pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549110439025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549110439023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_152519"," gameId":" 4b82873e-53b8-420f-9046-173919b0bc6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_pa..pa.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pa_mke-tha-pa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}